Guide to the History Department, Office Files, University of Pittsburgh, 1954-2010 UA.90.08.22.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
History Department, Office Files, University of Pittsburgh
1954-2010
ULS Archives & Special Collections
University of Pittsburgh. Department of History
UA.90.08.22.1
3.75 Linear Feet (3 Boxes)
This collection consists of office files from the History Department, University of Pittsburgh for the years 1954-2010.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Deposited by Dr. Van Beck Hall (Department Chair) on August 17, 2011.
Arrangement
These records were reviewed and arranged by Dr. Van Beck Hall for deposit in the University Archives. The Administrative Files are arranged by date and the other files by name or subject.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection consists of office files and administrative papers of the History Department from 1954-2010. It includes reports, correspondence, event announcements, minutes and notes of meetings, and curricula vitae of faculty.
Previous Citation
History Department, Office Files, University of Pittsburgh, 1954-2010, UA 90/08/22/1, University Archives, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Résumés (Personnel records); Correspondence; Universities and colleges -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh -- Records and correspondence; University of Pittsburgh; University of Pittsburgh. Department of History; University of Pittsburgh. Department of History -- Faculty; University of Pittsburgh. Department of History -- Records and correspondence
- Administrative Files, I.
  - 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 5-7)
  - 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
  - 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4-7)
  - 2001 (Box 2, Folder 8-10)
  - 2002 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
  - 2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Reports, II.
  - University Reports -- ROTC (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - University Reports -- Urban Studies (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - University Reports -- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Community Reports -- Pittsburgh Regional Oral History (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Community Reports -- Archives of Industrial Society (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - History Department Internal Reports (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
  - Other Reports (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, III.
  - 1957-1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1970-1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1992-2010 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Events, IV.
  - Events (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Meetings, V.
  - Departmental, 1954-1959 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Departmental, 1960-1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Departmental, 1970-1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Departmental, 1980-1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Departmental, 1994-1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Faculty, 1970-2006 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Division of the Social Sciences, 1960-1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Other, 1956-1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Curricula Vitae of Faculty, VI.
  - B (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - C-F (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - G-H (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - L (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - M (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - N-P (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - R (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - S-T (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - V-W (Box 3, Folder 29)